<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Practice on Synedrus</title><link>https://www.synedrus.com.au/practice/</link><description>Recent content in Practice on Synedrus</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-au</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 21:05:50 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.synedrus.com.au/practice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://www.synedrus.com.au/practice/about/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 21:05:50 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://www.synedrus.com.au/practice/about/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="at-synedrus-our-mission-is-clear-solve-urgent-technical-challenges-with-speed-expertise-and-tangible-results">At Synedrus, our mission is clear: Solve urgent technical challenges with speed, expertise, and tangible results.&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>We exist to address the real-world problems that threaten your operations—security vulnerabilities, delivery bottlenecks, audit pressures, and stalled projects. We do not focus on generic transformation initiatives. Instead, we prioritise immediate business impact, acting quickly and decisively to keep your business secure and on track.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="what-drives-us">What drives us:&lt;/h3>
&lt;h4 id="action-over-theory">Action over theory&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>We focus on the technical issues that matter most right now—unblocking releases, closing security gaps, and resolving critical delivery problems—so your business can move forward with confidence.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How We Work</title><link>https://www.synedrus.com.au/practice/how-we-work/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.synedrus.com.au/practice/how-we-work/</guid><description>&lt;p>When something is broken, risky, or blocking delivery, you don’t need a strategy roadmap. You need it fixed—fast, and properly.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Synedrus engagements are short, structured, and laser-focused on solving a specific technical problem.&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="what-to-expect">What to Expect&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Each engagement is structured as a fixed-scope sprint. No lock-in. No bloated process. Just the right structure to keep things clean and moving.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="1-discovery">1. Discovery&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We start with a quick email exchange to understand your goals, pain points, and where you’re stuck. If there’s alignment, we book a free 30-minute discovery call to explore the problem in more depth and outline possible paths forward. No obligation.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>