<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Synedrus</title><link>https://www.synedrus.com.au/</link><description>Recent content on Synedrus</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-au</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 21:05:50 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.synedrus.com.au/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://www.synedrus.com.au/practice/about/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 21:05:50 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://www.synedrus.com.au/practice/about/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="at-synedrus-our-mission-is-clear-solve-urgent-technical-challenges-with-speed-expertise-and-tangible-results">At Synedrus, our mission is clear: Solve urgent technical challenges with speed, expertise, and tangible results.&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>We exist to address the real-world problems that threaten your operations—security vulnerabilities, delivery bottlenecks, audit pressures, and stalled projects. We do not focus on generic transformation initiatives. Instead, we prioritise immediate business impact, acting quickly and decisively to keep your business secure and on track.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="what-drives-us">What drives us:&lt;/h3>
&lt;h4 id="action-over-theory">Action over theory&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>We focus on the technical issues that matter most right now—unblocking releases, closing security gaps, and resolving critical delivery problems—so your business can move forward with confidence.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What Good DevSecOps Looks Like</title><link>https://www.synedrus.com.au/insights/what-good-devsecops-looks-like/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:19:13 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://www.synedrus.com.au/insights/what-good-devsecops-looks-like/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Contact Us</title><link>https://www.synedrus.com.au/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.synedrus.com.au/contact/</guid><description>&lt;p>If security risks, stalled projects, or system failures are burning time and trust, reach out. We’ll discuss what’s wrong and how to fix it.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We’ll usually follow up with a couple of quick emails to clarify your goals — then schedule a free 30-minute discovery call to explore how we can help. No obligation — just a focused conversation to see if there’s a fit.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>For more detail on how engagements are structured, see &lt;a href="https://www.synedrus.com.au/practice/how-we-work/">How We Work&lt;/a>.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Disaster Readiness and Recovery</title><link>https://www.synedrus.com.au/services/disaster-readiness-and-recovery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.synedrus.com.au/services/disaster-readiness-and-recovery/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="dont-wait-for-a-crisis-to-find-out-you-werent-ready">Don’t wait for a crisis to find out you weren’t ready.&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>A small mistake—like an expired login, a broken update, or the wrong setting—can quietly take down part of your system.
The real question is: would anyone know? Would the right warnings go off? Would the system bounce back, or would everything grind to a halt?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This service safely simulates a real-world failure in your staging environment and shows you what your systems actually do when something goes wrong. No theory, but hard evidence of what works and what doesn&amp;rsquo;t.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How We Work</title><link>https://www.synedrus.com.au/practice/how-we-work/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.synedrus.com.au/practice/how-we-work/</guid><description>&lt;p>When something is broken, risky, or blocking delivery, you don’t need a strategy roadmap. You need it fixed—fast, and properly.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Synedrus engagements are short, structured, and laser-focused on solving a specific technical problem.&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="what-to-expect">What to Expect&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Each engagement is structured as a fixed-scope sprint. No lock-in. No bloated process. Just the right structure to keep things clean and moving.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="1-discovery">1. Discovery&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We start with a quick email exchange to understand your goals, pain points, and where you’re stuck. If there’s alignment, we book a free 30-minute discovery call to explore the problem in more depth and outline possible paths forward. No obligation.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Pre-Audit Remediation Sprint</title><link>https://www.synedrus.com.au/services/pre-audit-remediation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.synedrus.com.au/services/pre-audit-remediation/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="rapid-technical-hardening-to-eliminate-audit-blockers-and-prevent-compliance-red-flags">Rapid technical hardening to eliminate audit blockers and prevent compliance red flags.&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Compliance officers identify audit risks—they don’t usually fix them themselves. Your internal team could handle it, but they’re probably occupied with project work, maintenance, or urgent tasks.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>That’s where we step in.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This targeted service quickly addresses the critical technical vulnerabilities and configuration gaps that auditors zero in on. We fix security misconfigurations, tighten infrastructure, enforce access controls, and document every improvement clearly—making your audit smoother and less stressful.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://www.synedrus.com.au/legal/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.synedrus.com.au/legal/privacy-policy/</guid><description>&lt;p>This Privacy Policy describes our policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of your information when you use the Website and tells you about your privacy rights and how the law protects you.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We use your Personal data to provide services described on this Website. By using the Website, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We comply with the Australian Privacy Principles (APPs) under the Privacy Act 1988, which governs how we collect, use, disclose, and store personal information.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Security Hardening</title><link>https://www.synedrus.com.au/services/security-hardening/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.synedrus.com.au/services/security-hardening/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="targeted-security-intervention-to-prevent-the-breach-before-it-happens">Targeted security intervention to prevent the breach before it happens.&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This isn’t a penetration test or a compliance audit. It’s a focused, hands-on engagement to identify and remediate the highest-risk security issues in your .NET, Azure, or AWS environment—and fix what matters most.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Breaches often start with something simple: something not configured properly, a forgotten password, or an out-of-date service. Most companies don’t realise they’re exposed until it’s too late. This service is designed to mitigate that risk.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Stalled Project Rescue</title><link>https://www.synedrus.com.au/services/stalled-project-rescue/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.synedrus.com.au/services/stalled-project-rescue/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="when-your-project-is-stuck-and-time-is-running-out-we-get-it-moving">When your project is stuck and time is running out, we get it moving.&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Software projects stall for all kinds of reasons: Sometimes the plan wasn’t clear. Sometimes the tech didn’t work. Sometimes the team just ran out of time.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Whatever the reason, the result is the same: deadlines slip, costs rise, and confidence drops.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We help businesses break that deadlock.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This service is designed to cut through the noise, identify exactly what’s blocking progress, and deliver a working solution to move things forward.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Thank You</title><link>https://www.synedrus.com.au/thank-you/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.synedrus.com.au/thank-you/</guid><description>&lt;p>Your message has been received — we appreciate your interest and will be in touch shortly.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In the meantime, feel free to explore more about how Synedrus helps companies architect secure, scalable systems by returning to the &lt;a href="https://www.synedrus.com.au/">homepage&lt;/a> to continue browsing.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>