<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Synedrus</title><link>https://synedrus.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Synedrus</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-au</language><atom:link href="https://synedrus.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cloud Architecture</title><link>https://synedrus.github.io/services/cloud-architecture/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://synedrus.github.io/services/cloud-architecture/</guid><description>&lt;p>Many cloud setups grow messy, costly, and complex. You end up paying more while delivering less, held back by shaky foundations and technical debt.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We fix this by providing sharp architectural guidance, rapid prototyping, and clear, validated solutions your internal teams can execute with confidence.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Whether you&amp;rsquo;re building a greenfield platform with ambitious, innovative features that needs to scale cleanly from day one, or you&amp;rsquo;re stuck with a bloated, fragile system that needs to be rescued and rebuilt, we step in with strategic firepower and no-nonsense architectural execution.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Contact Us</title><link>https://synedrus.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://synedrus.github.io/contact/</guid><description>&lt;p>Ready to strengthen your cloud systems or tackle your next big project? Get in touch to discuss your needs.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We’ll usually follow up with a couple of quick emails to clarify your goals - then schedule a free 30-minute discovery call to explore how we can help. No obligation - just a focused conversation to see if there’s a fit.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>For more detail on how engagements are structured, see &lt;a href="https://synedrus.github.io/about/how-we-work/">How We Work&lt;/a>.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>DevSecOps</title><link>https://synedrus.github.io/services/devsecops/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://synedrus.github.io/services/devsecops/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>Your apps have changed. Has your security kept pace?&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Modern applications are built differently. They&amp;rsquo;re faster, more complex, and far more connected - which makes them easier targets. Each piece of your tech stack introduces another opportunity for attackers to strike. Yet most businesses are still relying on outdated security methods, using slow manual checks and old - school tools that don’t fit today’s digital landscape.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The uncomfortable truth? Your security team is stretched thin, your engineers see security as someone else’s responsibility, and every deployment risks becoming tomorrow’s headline - making breach.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Digital Transformation</title><link>https://synedrus.github.io/services/digital-transformation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://synedrus.github.io/services/digital-transformation/</guid><description>&lt;p>Modernising technology isn’t just about adopting the latest tools - it’s about aligning architecture, security, and delivery to drive real business outcomes.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>At Synedrus, digital transformation means helping organisations move with precision: scaling systems smoothly, securing delivery pipelines, and reworking processes so teams can deliver confidently under pressure. We work with SaaS companies, tech-driven businesses, and ambitious mid-market firms that need transformation to happen &lt;em>without&lt;/em> waste, delays, or unnecessary complexity.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How We Work</title><link>https://synedrus.github.io/about/how-we-work/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://synedrus.github.io/about/how-we-work/</guid><description>&lt;p>Synedrus delivers sharp, strategic consulting - not bloated delivery teams or endless implementation cycles. Every engagement is lean, focused, and structured to give you architectural clarity, validated direction, and the ability to move fast with confidence.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Here’s what working with us looks like:&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="1-discovery">1. Discovery&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>We start with a quick email exchange to understand your goals, pain points, and where you’re stuck. If there’s alignment, we book a free 30-minute discovery call to explore the problem in more depth and outline possible paths forward. No obligation.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Our Mission</title><link>https://synedrus.github.io/about/our-mission/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://synedrus.github.io/about/our-mission/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="at-synedrus-our-mission-is-simple">At Synedrus, our mission is simple&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>To deliver expert cloud architecture, embedded security, and strategic clarity - helping ambitious companies scale, modernise, and secure their systems with confidence.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We believe digital transformation isn’t about buying the flashiest tools or following every trend. It’s about building clean, resilient systems that serve clear business goals.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="what-drives-us">What drives us:&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Precision over complexity&lt;/strong> - Every design choice should cut waste, not create it.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Security as a foundation, not an afterthought&lt;/strong> - We embed secure practices from day one, because trust and resilience are non-negotiable.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://synedrus.github.io/legal/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://synedrus.github.io/legal/privacy-policy/</guid><description>&lt;p>This Privacy Policy describes our policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of your information when you use the Website and tells you about your privacy rights and how the law protects you.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We use your Personal data to provide services described on this Website. By using the Website, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We comply with the Australian Privacy Principles (APPs) under the Privacy Act 1988, which governs how we collect, use, disclose, and store personal information.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Thank You</title><link>https://synedrus.github.io/thank-you/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://synedrus.github.io/thank-you/</guid><description>&lt;p>Your message has been received - we appreciate your interest and will be in touch shortly.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In the meantime, feel free to explore more about how Synedrus helps companies architect secure, scalable systems by returning to the &lt;a href="https://synedrus.github.io/">homepage&lt;/a> to continue browsing.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Who We Are</title><link>https://synedrus.github.io/about/who-we-are/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://synedrus.github.io/about/who-we-are/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://www.placehold.co/270x400" alt="Portrait Placeholder" title="Portrait" style="float:left; margin:0 1rem 0.2rem 0;">
&lt;p>Michail Konstantinidis is a technologist with nearly 20 years of software development experience across London and Sydney, working across industries like finance, SaaS, property management, entertainment, and automotive. Over time, it became clear that delivering meaningful outcomes required more than just writing code — it required stepping beyond narrow delivery roles to engage with architecture, security, and strategy at a systems level.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As a technical lead, Michail has guided teams through mission-critical projects, balancing technical excellence with real-world delivery demands under tight timelines and evolving requirements. This experience shaped Synedrus&amp;rsquo;s core approach: deliver sharp, expert-led solutions that cut through complexity and focus on what truly moves projects forward.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>