<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Services on Synedrus</title><link>https://www.synedrus.com.au/services/</link><description>Recent content in Services on Synedrus</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-au</language><atom:link href="https://www.synedrus.com.au/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Disaster Readiness and Recovery</title><link>https://www.synedrus.com.au/services/disaster-readiness-and-recovery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.synedrus.com.au/services/disaster-readiness-and-recovery/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="dont-wait-for-a-crisis-to-find-out-you-werent-ready">Don’t wait for a crisis to find out you weren’t ready.&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>A small mistake, like an expired login, a broken update, or the wrong setting, can quietly take down part of your system.
The real question is: would anyone know? Would the right warnings go off? Would the system bounce back, or would everything grind to a halt?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This service safely simulates a real-world failure in your staging environment and shows you what your systems actually do when something goes wrong. No theory, but hard evidence of what works and what doesn&amp;rsquo;t.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Pre-Audit Remediation Sprint</title><link>https://www.synedrus.com.au/services/pre-audit-remediation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.synedrus.com.au/services/pre-audit-remediation/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="rapid-technical-hardening-to-eliminate-audit-blockers-and-prevent-compliance-red-flags">Rapid technical hardening to eliminate audit blockers and prevent compliance red flags.&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Compliance officers identify audit risks, they don’t usually fix them themselves. Your internal team could handle it, but they’re probably occupied with project work, maintenance, or urgent tasks.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>That’s where we step in.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This targeted service quickly addresses the critical technical vulnerabilities and configuration gaps that auditors zero in on. We fix security misconfigurations, tighten infrastructure, enforce access controls, and document every improvement clearly, making your audit smoother and less stressful.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Security Hardening</title><link>https://www.synedrus.com.au/services/security-hardening/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.synedrus.com.au/services/security-hardening/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="targeted-security-intervention-to-prevent-the-breach-before-it-happens">Targeted security intervention to prevent the breach before it happens.&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This isn’t a penetration test or a compliance audit. It’s a focused, hands-on engagement to identify and remediate the highest-risk security issues in your .NET, Azure, or AWS environment, and fix what matters most.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Breaches often start with something simple: something not configured properly, a forgotten password, or an out-of-date service. Most companies don’t realise they’re exposed until it’s too late. This service is designed to mitigate that risk.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Stalled Project Rescue</title><link>https://www.synedrus.com.au/services/stalled-project-rescue/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.synedrus.com.au/services/stalled-project-rescue/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="when-your-project-is-stuck-and-time-is-running-out-we-get-it-moving">When your project is stuck and time is running out, we get it moving.&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Software projects stall for all kinds of reasons: Sometimes the plan wasn’t clear. Sometimes the tech didn’t work. Sometimes the team just ran out of time.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Whatever the reason, the result is the same: deadlines slip, costs rise, and confidence drops.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We help businesses break that deadlock.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This service is designed to cut through the noise, identify exactly what’s blocking progress, and deliver a working solution to move things forward.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>