<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About on Synedrus</title><link>https://www.synedrus.com.au/about/</link><description>Recent content in About on Synedrus</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-au</language><atom:link href="https://www.synedrus.com.au/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How We Work</title><link>https://www.synedrus.com.au/about/how-we-work/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.synedrus.com.au/about/how-we-work/</guid><description>&lt;p>Synedrus delivers sharp, strategic consulting - not bloated delivery teams or endless implementation cycles. Every engagement is lean, focused, and structured to give you architectural clarity, validated direction, and the ability to move fast with confidence.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Here’s what working with us looks like:&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="1-discovery">1. Discovery&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>We start with a quick email exchange to understand your goals, pain points, and where you’re stuck. If there’s alignment, we book a free 30-minute discovery call to explore the problem in more depth and outline possible paths forward. No obligation.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Our Mission</title><link>https://www.synedrus.com.au/about/our-mission/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.synedrus.com.au/about/our-mission/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="at-synedrus-our-mission-is-simple">At Synedrus, our mission is simple&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>To deliver expert cloud architecture, embedded security, and strategic clarity - helping ambitious companies scale, modernise, and secure their systems with confidence.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We believe digital transformation isn’t about buying the flashiest tools or following every trend. It’s about building clean, resilient systems that serve clear business goals.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="what-drives-us">What drives us:&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Precision over complexity&lt;/strong> - Every design choice should cut waste, not create it.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Security as a foundation, not an afterthought&lt;/strong> - We embed secure practices from day one, because trust and resilience are non-negotiable.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Who We Are</title><link>https://www.synedrus.com.au/about/who-we-are/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.synedrus.com.au/about/who-we-are/</guid><description>&lt;p>Michail Konstantinidis is a technologist with nearly 20 years of software development experience across London and Sydney, working across industries like finance, SaaS, property management, entertainment, and automotive. Over time, it became clear that delivering meaningful outcomes required more than just writing code — it required stepping beyond narrow delivery roles to engage with architecture, security, and strategy at a systems level.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As a technical lead, Michail has guided teams through mission-critical projects, balancing technical excellence with real-world delivery demands under tight timelines and evolving requirements. This experience shaped Synedrus&amp;rsquo;s core approach: deliver sharp, expert-led solutions that cut through complexity and focus on what truly moves projects forward.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>